juiceinthecity.com 2012-06-23

# Juice In the City Privacy Policy

### Juice In The City Privacy Policy

Juice In The City will definitely protect your privacy! Following are the rules about what information the Juice In The City websites (collectively, the “Website”) collects from you (the “User”) and how we use that information.

#### Types of Information

Personally Identifiable Information. Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies a you as an individual (the “User”). When you engage in certain activities on the Website, you will be asked to provide certain personal information about yourself, such as your name, email address, telephone number and date of birth and more. When you order products or services, we may also ask you to provide us with your credit card number, expiration date and authentication codes or related information. These are all forms of Personally Identifiable Information. We use Personally Identifiable Information to provide products and services to you, improve our Website and products, and to improve your experience with third parties (See section 3 below). If you use our Website to send information or a product to another person, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of any recipient and use it to allow the recipient to access the information you requested we send. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you, enforce our agreements with you, including our Website Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. If you send our customer service an email we may use your comments to tell others about our services, and may post your comment in our marketing materials or on our Website. If you choose to include Personally Identifiable Information in those emails, that Personally Identifiable Information may be included.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify a specific User, like the URL of the websites you visit before and after coming to our Website, your browser, IP address etc. We, and our third party service providers and advertisers, may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website as described below. We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, administer the Website, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable law etc. We may also share this information with our authorized third party service providers and advertisers.

#### Release of Information

We will not share your information with other parties, except when: 

We may share your Personally Identifiable information with Juice In The City Vendors. We provide deals from merchants (“Juice In the City Vendors”). Sometimes we provide offers from particular merchants who, as part of the deal offer, request information on JITC customers who purchased the offer. In those cases, we share some of your Personally Identifiable Information with those Juice In The City Vendors. Sharing this Information will allow a Juice In The City Vendor to market directly to you should they choose to do so. We will only provide a Juice In The City Vendor information other than your name with an opt-in notice to you, in which you will have a chance to choose that Juice In The City not give the Juice In The City Vendor the rest of your personal information. While we inform them that they are only permitted to communicate with you for the purposes of the specific promotion with JITC, if they do market directly to you in the future without your permission, we disclaim any responsibility or liability for the actions of such Juice In The City Vendor. 

We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with Authorized Third Party Service Providers. We provide some of our services and products through third parties who send out and distribute our administrative and promotional emails. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such service providers to fulfill orders, send emails, control email lists, analyze data, search results, process credit card payments, provide customer service and more. We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies with whom we have business relationships and may have to also share their information with service providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. For example, when you order a service, we release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for the service. The use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties is not subject to our control.

We may share your Personally Identifiable Information for our Protection and the Protection of Others. We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law or a court order; enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, our Website Terms of Use or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others.

**Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Partners, Affiliates and Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information with “Third Party Advertisers” and their service providers. We use such service providers to serve ads when you visit our Website and they may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. We also use third party service providers to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. 

#### Collection and Use of Information

You can always choose not to provide information, although it may be required to engage in a certain activity on the Website. As a condition of purchase of our products and services, we will send you Administrative and Promotional emails. We will send you information regarding your account activity and purchases as well as updates about our products and promotional offers. You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. However, you do have a choice with respect to Promotional Emails that advertise our products and services, including exclusive sales and other offers, and/or the products and services of our Advertisers and Affiliates. If you do not want to receive Promotional Emails from us, you may elect to opt-out of receiving Promotional Emails at any time after registering by emailing us at contact@juiceinthecity.com, by writing to us at the address contained herein, or by hitting the “unsubscribe” button at the bottom of any of our e-mails. 

#### Security of Information

We take security seriously and take numerous precautions to protect the security of Personally Identifiable Information. Your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. We encrypt certain sensitive information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information is safe as it is transmitted to us. 

#### Data Tracking

**Cookies.**  
To facilitate and customize your experience with the Website as well as allow third party advertisers to display ads, we store cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a User’s computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser.

**Other Tracking Devices.**  
We may use other industry standard technologies like pixel tags and web beacons to track your use of our Website pages and promotions, or we may allow our Third Party Service Providers to use these devices on our behalf. Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certain pages on our Website, or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. When you access these pages or open or click an email, pixel tags and web beacons generate a Non-Personally Identifiable notice of that action. Pixel tags allow us to measure and improve our understanding of visitor traffic and behavior on our Website, as well as give us a way to measure our promotions and performance. We may also utilize pixel tags and web beacons provided by our Affiliates and/or Marketing Partners for the same purposes.

#### Miscellaneous Privacy Issues

**Children.**  
Minors under the age of 18 may not use the Website. We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known to be under the age of 18, and no part of the Website is designed to attract anyone under the age of 18. Juice In The City does not sell products for purchase by children. In certain instances, we sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use Juice In The City only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Public Areas.**  
We may provide areas on our Website where you can publicly post information about yourself, can communicate with others, or can review products, restaurants, and submit media content. This information may be accessible by other consumers and companies and may appear on other websites or web searches, and therefore this information could be read, collected, and used by others. For example, if you post your email address along with a public restaurant review, you may receive unsolicited messages. We have no control over who reads your postings or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any personal information.

**Notice of Privacy Rights to California Residents.**  
California law requires that we provide you with a summary of your privacy rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (the "Act") and the California Business and Professions Code. As required by the Act, we will provide you with the categories of Personally Identifiable Information that we collect through the Website and the categories of third party persons or entities with whom such Personally Identifiable Information may be shared for direct marketing purposes at your request. California law requires us to inform you, at your request, (1) the categories of Personally Identifiable Information we collect and what third parties we share that information with; (2) the names and addresses of those third parties; and (3) examples of the products marketed by those companies. The Act further requires us to allow you to control who you do not want us to share that information with. To obtain this information, please send a request by email or standard mail to the address found below. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Personally Identifiable Information you do not want us to share with Affiliated Businesses or Marketing Partners. The request should be sent to the attention of our legal department, and labeled “California Customer Choice Notice.” Please allow 30 days for a response. Also, please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information or requesting this notice.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. It is the responsibility of each User to review the Website periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. 

By using our website, you agree that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound to all the terms of this policy. If you do not agree, please leave the site and do not enter any information herein. 

#### For Customers

For customer service inquiries, please Contact us.
